<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><definition><schema><name>appliccrossreftable</name><title>Applicability Cross-reference Table</title><definition>The Applicability Cross-reference Table (ACT) data module is the central point of reference for applicability definitions when applicability filtering is required for either customized deliveries or filtering by a viewer.</definition><chapter>4.14.1</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-14-0100-00A-040A-A_004-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>brex</name><title>Business Rules Exchange</title><definition>The mechanism is a means to communicate business rules that have been developed and agreed within a project or organization.</definition><chapter>4.10</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-10-0000-00A-040A-A_005-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>checklist</name><title>Maintenance Checklists and Inspections</title><definition>This Schema is used to capture and represent maintenance planning information but includes key elements to provide additional functionality. It provides the ability to reduce failure by providing a list of operations or checks to be performed for maintaining the Product. The schema can be used for checklist and inspection information such as scheduled inspection and maintenance conditions necessary to keep the equipment in serviceable condition. It includes a special category to identify in what instances the equipment is not ready or usable.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.14</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-14A-040A-A_004-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>comment</name><title>Comment</title><definition>Commenting and reporting on issues raised on data modules or publication modules during the verification process and the in-service phase of the Product can be done using the comment form. This form is compiled by the commenting authority and sent to the issuing authority of the data modules or publication modules. The comment form is also used to provide a response to the originator of the comment.</definition><chapter>4.6</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-06-0000-00A-040A-A_008-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>comrep</name><title>Common Information Repository</title><definition>The Common Information Repository (CIR) data modules are listing common information objects of a certain type (eg, parts, zones, warnings) with their description. Each object is accompanied with an extensive set of properties (eg, name, short name in the Part or the Zone CIR), its full wording (eg, warning text and caution text in the Warning and the Caution CIR) or applicability annotations (applicability statements in the Externalized applicability annotation CIR).</definition><chapter>4.13.1</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-13-0100-00A-040A-A_004-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>condcrossreftable</name><title>Conditions Cross-reference Table</title><definition>The Conditions Cross-reference Table (CCT) data module is used to declare conditions that have an affect on the applicability of data and is used to define the incorporation status for technical conditions.</definition><chapter>4.14.2</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-14-0200-00A-040A-A_004-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>container</name><title>Container</title><definition>The container data module is a production management mechanism to associate several data modules representing the same data.</definition><chapter>4.13.4</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-13-0400-00A-040A-A_005-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>crew</name><title>Crew/Operator Information</title><definition>The Crew Schema is provided for the production of Crew/Operator information such as description and operation of the Product, flight and sequential information.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.6</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-06A-040A-A_008-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>dc</name><title></title><definition></definition><chapter></chapter><para></para><DMC></DMC></schema><schema><name>ddn</name><title>Data Dispatch Note</title><definition>The data dispatch note defines the sender, the receiver and the content of the dispatch.</definition><chapter>7.5.1</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-07-05-0100-00A-040A-A_007-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>descript</name><title>Descriptive</title><definition>This Schema is used to capture and represent descriptive information.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.2</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-02A-040A-A_008-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>dml</name><title>Data Management List</title><definition>A Data Management Requirement List (DMRL) is used to identify the required data modules and, by project decision, publication modules for a project. The data management requirement list supports planning, reporting, production and configuration control, especially in a work share environment. A data management requirement list can be generated in parts (eg, by partner companies for later merging) or in a complete form.<br/>The purpose of a CSDB Status List (CSL) is to exchange information about the status of the CSDB.</definition><chapter>4.5</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-05-0000-00A-040A-A_006-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>fault</name><title>Fault Information</title><definition>The fault Schema is used to capture and represent fault reporting, fault isolation and fault correlation information.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.4</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-04A-040A-A_008-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>frontmatter</name><title>Front Matter</title><definition>The Front matter Schema described in this chapter can be used to minimize manual authoring and in most cases support auto-generation of the Front matter data modules.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.16</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-16A-040A-A_002-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>ipd</name><title>Illustrated Parts Data</title><definition>The IPD Schema is to be used to capture and represent parts lists and IPD. This information can be drawn from an S2000M provisioning database or from engineering data for a non-S2000M project.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.7</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-07A-040A-A_009-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>learning</name><title>Learning</title><definition>In S1000D, the support for managing learning information reflects how the information is structured and managed in accordance with Sharable Content Object Reference Model (SCORM). The incentive is to use a CSDB for managing learning information with same degree of control as applied to the technical publications.</definition><chapter>4.15</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-15-0000-00A-040A-A_002-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>pm</name><title>Publication Module</title><definition>In order to define, prepare and manage publications generated of data modules, S1000D uses the publication module.</definition><chapter>4.9</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-09-0000-00A-040A-A_007-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>prdcrossreftable</name><title>Products Cross-reference Table</title><definition>The Products Cross-reference Table (PCT) data module is a repository of product instances and the values for product attributes and conditions for each product instance.</definition><chapter>4.14.3</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-14-0300-00A-040A-A_004-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>proced</name><title>Procedural</title><definition>The procedural Schema is used to capture and represent procedural information. The granularity of maintenance procedural data modules must follow the breakdown reflected by the SNS and the information codes, and must reflect the tasks identified in the maintenance plan. The granularity of crew/operator procedural data modules must follow the breakdown reflected by the SNS and the information codes, and must reflect the operations identified.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.3</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-03A-040A-A_008-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>process</name><title>Process</title><definition>The S1000D process data module represents a procedural flow consisting of several data modules and/or steps that are sequenced. Decision points (branching), looping, and selective filtering are supported. An interface to external applications which can return results to direct procedural flow is supported. The process data module can be considered a procedural flow script.</definition><chapter>4.11</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-11-0000-00A-040A-A_005-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>rdf</name><title></title><definition></definition><chapter></chapter><para></para><DMC></DMC></schema><schema><name>sb</name><title>Service Bulletin</title><definition>The service bulletin Schema is used to capture and represent service bulletin information.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.15</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-15A-040A-A_002-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>schedul</name><title>Maintenance Planning</title><definition>This Schema is used to capture and represent maintenance planning information.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.5</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-05A-040A-A_009-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>scocontent</name><title>SCORM content information</title><definition>The SCO content Schema is composed of elements used to provide references to external SCO or S1000D managed references defining a hierarchy of training steps.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.17</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-17A-040A-A_001-80_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>scormcontentpackage</name><title>SCORM Content Package Module</title><definition>The SCPM is used to define the hierarchical structure of learning events within a course or learning product. To be more representative of how training is packaged for use in a Learning Management System (LMS), certain element names in the SCORM content package module have been modified, and new elements have been added.</definition><chapter>4.15.1</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-15-0100-00A-040A-A_002-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>update</name><title>Incremental Update of CIR</title><definition>The Data update file is a dedicated type of CSDB object. This file can be used to deliver fragments from a given Common Information Repository (CIR) data module. These fragments correspond to the ones that have been added, deleted, modified or reinstated since a previous issue of the CIR data module.</definition><chapter>4.13.2</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-13-0200-00A-040A-A_004-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>wrngdata</name><title>Wiring Data</title><definition>The wiring data Schema is used to capture and represent the wiring data of the Product such as wire data, harness data, electrical equipment data and standard parts data.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.9.1</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-09A-040A-A_008-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>wrngflds</name><title>Wiring Data Description</title><definition>The wiring data description Schema is used for configuration and declaration of the elements of the wiring data Schema.</definition><chapter>3.9.5.2.9.13</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0502-09P-040A-A_005-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>xcf</name><title>WebCGM 2.0 XML Companion File</title><definition>WebCGM 2.0 includes an external companion file that enables control of the behavior of the WebCGM viewer through an XML DOM interface.</definition><chapter>7.3.2</chapter><para></para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-07-03-0200-00A-040A-A_005-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>xlink</name><title></title><definition></definition><chapter></chapter><para></para><DMC></DMC></schema><schema><name>brDoc</name><title>Business rules document</title><definition>The data module provides a means to create and manage the business rules developed by a project, enterprise, etc. The basic structure is inherited from the descriptive data module, however enhanced to facilitate a structured representation of business rules and business rules decision points, as well as information valuable in the business rules development process.</definition><chapter>4.10.1.</chapter><para>1</para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-04-10-0100-00A-040A-A_005-00_EN-US</DMC></schema><schema><name>icnMetadata</name><title>Illustration rules and multimedia - ICN metadata file</title><definition>The ICN metadata file contains metadata related to an ICN object, ie, illustration or multimedia object.</definition><chapter>3.9.2.7</chapter><para>1</para><DMC>DMC-S1000D-A-03-09-0207-00A-040A-A_001-00_EN-US</DMC></schema></definition>